Bakke, E. Wight Papers 5522
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Student Political Activism in Venezuela (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Tomasson, Richard F. and Eric Allardt, Student Politics and Higher Education in Scandinavia (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Walter, Richard J., Argentina and Peru (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Brookings Material (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Collective Bargaining - 62b (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Department of Labor (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Draft, Not for Citation (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Employment Policies of the U.S. and Japan (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Foreign Exp. (Box 35, Folder 7)
- High Talent Manpower Policy (Box 35, Folder 8)
- High Talent Manpower Policy (Box 35, Folder 9)
- High Talent Manpower Policy, Outline (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Inter-federal Manpower and Employment Agency Relations (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Manpower and Employment Stability (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Manpower and Social Affairs Committee, United Kingdom (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Manpower Conference (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Manpower, General Nature of Manpower Policy and Program (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Manpower Material (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Manpower Policy Premises (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Manpower Policy Task Force (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Manpower Policy Task Force #1 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Manpower Poverty and Activities (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Manpower Upjohn - Bakke, Memos and Notes for Books (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Items, Employment Service (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Speeches (Box 35, Folder 24)
- MPT #2 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- MPT #3 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- MPT #4 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- MPT #5 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- National Manpower Minutes and Working Papers (Box 35, Folder 29)
- National Manpower Policy, E.W.B. (Box 35, Folder 30)
- National Manpower Policy Task Force (Box 35, Folder 31)
- National Manpower Policy Task Force (Box 35, Folder 32)
- National Manpower Policy Task Force, Meetings, Correspondence and Papers and Minutes and Business including ideas for program, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  For Tapes of Conferences see Box 38
- National Manpower Policy Task Force, Meetings, Correspondence and Papers and Minutes and Business including ideas for program, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  For Tapes of Conferences see Box 39
- Notes and Contacts (Box 36, Folder 3)
- O.E.C.D. Conference, Draft of Tape (Box 36, Folder 4)
- O.E.C.D. Conference, London, February 1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  February
- O.E.C.D. Correspondence of S. Berlin (Box 36, Folder 6)
- O.E.C.D. Economic Implications of Training Programmes (Box 36, Folder 7)
- O.E.C.D. Economic Outlook #2, December 1967 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- O.E.C.D. Economic Outlook #4, December 1968 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- O.E.C.D. Industrial Production #4, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- O.E.C.D. International Conference on Employment Fluctuations and Manpower Policy (Box 36, Folder 11)
- O.E.C.D. International Conference on Employment Fluctuations and Manpower Policy, 1-9 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- O.E.C.D. International Seminar on Active Manpower Policy, April 14-17, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  April 14-17
- O.E.C.D. International Seminar on Active Manpower Policy, April 14-17, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- O.E.C.D. International Management Seminar on Active Manpower Policy, Report 1-Supplement (Box 36, Folder 15)
- O.E.C.D. International Seminar (Trade Union) on Active Labour Market Policy, Vienna, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  Sept. 17th-20th
- O.E.C.D. International Trade Union Seminar on Active Manpower Policy (Box 36, Folder 17)
- O.E.C.D. Labor Force Statistics (Box 36, Folder 18)
- O.E.C.D. London Meeting (Box 36, Folder 19)
- O.E.C.D. Main Economic Indicators #1, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  January
- O.E.C.D. Main Economic Indicators #2 + 4, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- O.E.C.D. Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 22)
- O.E.C.D. Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 23)
- O.E.C.D. Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 24)
- O.E.C.D. Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 25)
- O.E.C.D. Observer (Box 36, Folder 26)
- OEECD Speech (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Original Draft (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Policy with Respect to Integration (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Preliminary Draft (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Proposed Policy for Employment and Manpower Agency (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Sweden Data (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Task Force (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Task Force Memoranda Including those of E.W.B. (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Washington, DC, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  Sept. 17th
- American Studies, Parts I - III: Salzburg Seminar, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- American Studies, Parts I - III: Salzburg Seminar, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- American Studies, Parts I - III: Salzburg Seminar, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Bureau of Research and Statistics (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Committee on Research in Medical Economics (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Conference on Theory of Organization (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Connecticut Citizen's Committee of the ARTS, Sciences and Professions (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Cornell University, NYSSILR Planning Committee (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Current Problems in Labor Relations Law School of Yale University (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Friends Service Committee (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Friends Service Committee (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Friends Service Committee (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Friends University Center (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Friends Work Camps (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Governor's Special Committee (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Graduate Education for Women at Yale, Parts I and II (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Graduate Education for Women at Yale, Parts I and II (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Goth of the Community Pendle Hill Summer Session (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Holland, Select Sub-Committee on Labor, 1964-1967 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Industrial Relations Center, University of Michigan, Directors Luncheon (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Industrial Relations Research Association (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Labor Productivity, International Economic Association Conference, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  Sept. 12th
- National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Post War Planning Committee, Reports and Original Plans (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Post War Planning Committee, Reports and Original Plans (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Post War Planning Committee, Reports and Original Plans (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Post War Planning Committee, Reports and Original Plans (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Post War Planning Committee, Reports and Original Plans (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Post War Planning Committee (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Post War Universal Military Training Council (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Princeton University Conference, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  May-June
- Public Employee Relations, Parts I-IV, Governor Rockefeller's Commission (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Public Employee Relations, Parts I-IV, Governor Rockefeller's Commission (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Public Employee Relations, Parts I-IV, Governor Rockefeller's Commission (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Public Employee Relations, Parts I-IV, Governor Rockefeller's Commission (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Riverside Church Form, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  Nov. 10th
- Role of Industrial Relations, Industrial Relations Research Institute (Box 38, Folder 9)
- The Rudge Audit of Organizational Effectiveness (Box 38, Folder 10)
- The Rudge Audit of Organizational Effectiveness (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Saposs, David J., Symposium (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Social Security Research Council, Conference for Research on Industrial Relations, Cornell, NY State School Conference, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Teacher-Board of Education Relationships (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Training in Business and Industry, Purdue University (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Unemployment and the American Economy (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Unemployment and the American Economy, 2nd Conference (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Labor Management Center, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Labor Management Center, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Labor Management Center, Announcements (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Labor Management Center, Articles (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Labor Management Center, Certificates (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Labor Management Center, Education Committee Report, LMC (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Labor Management Center, Employees Hiring Practices, Policies and Preferences (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Labor Management Center, Fellowships for Trade Union Leaders (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Labor Management Center, Financial (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Labor Management Center, General File (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Labor Management Center, Index for Pam. File (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Labor Management Center, Inventory (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Labor Management Center, Policy Committee Minutes (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Labor Management Center, Prospectus (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Labor Management Center, Reports (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Labor Management Center, Reports to the President (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Labor Management Center, Research Projects (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Bituminous Coal Emergency Board (Box 39, Folder 1)
  Enclosed Box I-XXV Tapes of O.E.C.D. Conference; see Box 36
- Bituminous Coal Emergency Board (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Bituminous Coal Emergency Board (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Bituminous Coal Emergency Board (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Economic and Sociology Courses (Box 40, Folder 1)
  including handouts, lecture notes, class lists and grade records
- Economic and Sociology Courses (Box 41, Folder 1)
- General Files (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Includes: Material used in courses, published material by Bakke, and topic material such as "employment."
- General Files (Box 43, Folder 1)
- General Files (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Reference material used in teaching courses, includes bibliographies (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Indian and Negro, Sec. 22 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Slavery (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Reconstruction (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Education (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Religion (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Murals and Marriages (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Crime (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Negro II, Immigration I (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Civil Rights (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Inferiority (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Negro Attitude (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Japanese Explanation (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Villano (Box 47, Folder 3)
- McKenna (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Socially (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Economic (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Independence and Control (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Vitality (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Back to Africa (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Race Mixture (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Solutions (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Immigration II, Sec. 22 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Poles (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Jews (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Chinese (Box 47, Folder 15)
- German, Norwegian (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Restructure (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Summary (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Journey and Ellis Sale (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Crime, Police Methods (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Industry and Occupation (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Religion (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Family (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Politics (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Community (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Health (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Mentally Deficient (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Introduction (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Causes of Poverty (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Social Insurance (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Housing (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Section III (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Social Adaptation (Box 48, Folder 10)
- British Labor Movement (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Fascism (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Employers Organization (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Industrial Democracy (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Cooperative Movement (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Japanese People (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Economic Planning (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Inter-racial Commission (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Farm Holiday (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Civil Disobedience (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Impact (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Examples of Democracy (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Japan (Box 49, Folder 4)
- In Students on the March (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Organization (Box 49, Folder 6)
- India (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Sinai Book, Egypt and Japan (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Egypt Notes (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Egypt Islam and Bibliography (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Modern Social Condition, Old Course (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Soc. Negro (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Social Science General (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Labor (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Labor History (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Negro (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Self Maintenance (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Family (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Housing (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Pathology (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Indian (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Government (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Unemployment (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Education (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Religion (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Student (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Negro Case Work, Student Reports (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Negro General Reference (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Art (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Bibliographies (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Education and Folk Beliefs (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Harlem (Box 49, Folder 33)
- History (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Industry (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Literature (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Kerr Case Book (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Mental Status and Race Traits (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Music (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Press (Box 49, Folder 40)
- Indian (Box 50, Folder 1)
- A. Reprints (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Student Politics (Box 50, Folder 3)
- B. E. Witte Bakke (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Self-Maintenance (Box 50, Folder 5)
- J.B.) - Student Image (Box 50, Folder 6)
- A.5) - Operational Values (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Independence and Control (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Youth Organization (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Activities, Issues: Mexico (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Demonstrations (Box 51, Folder 5)
- India (Box 51, Folder 6)
- France (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Student Leaders (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Law Graduates in Government (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Leadership and Political Institutions in India (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Students on the March (Box 52, Folder 1)
- French West Africa (Box 52, Folder 2)
- History of Trade Union (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Counseling, Giving Information to the Applicant (Box 52, Folder 4)
- British West Indies (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Function of Management and Executive Development (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Reprints on Princeton File (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Bonds of Organization (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Objectives of Employment Service (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Urban Rec. (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Views of Representative Organizations (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Unemployment Insurance (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Summary of N.A.M. Conventions, 1903-1927 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Administrative Conditions (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Minority Report (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Unmarried Cohabitations (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Unemployment Insurance, England (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Old-Age Assistance and Old-Age Benefits (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Human Needs (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Juvenile Court (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Juvenile Offenders (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Criminals (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Nature of Labor Legislation (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Urban Crime (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Negro Criminal (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Children's Bureau, Department of Labor, 1920 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Relief and Economic Trends, Michigan (Box 54, Folder 11)